So we tested that withdrawing eath when there's a single funder works perfectly,
我们已经测试了当只有一个资助者时提取以太币的情况，测试结果十分完美
let's test withdrawing eath if there are multiple funders,
现在让我们测试一下当存在多个资助者时提取以太币的情况
so we'll do it, let's say allows us to withdraw with multiple funders. Why would this be an async function.
所以我们就 `it("allows us to withdraw with multiple funders", async function() {})`
And let's do this await Funmi not fun,
让我们再次运行这个 `await fundMe.fund()`
but with a number of different accounts.
但这次有数个不同的账户
So we can create a whole bunch of different accounts of course,
所以我们需要创建一大堆不同的账户，这是当然的了
by saying const accounts equals await ethers dot get signers.
`const accounts = await ethers.getSigners()`
And we can loop through these accounts
我们可以遍历这些账户
and have each one of these accounts call the fund function.
并让它们中的每一个都调用这个 `fund` 函数
And we're going to do this with a for loop.
我们将使用一个 "for" 循环来实现这一操作
So we're going to say for let i equals
所以就是 `for (let i = )`
we'll start with the first index of the accounts
我们将从账户的第一个索引开始
because the zero with index is going to be the Deployer.
因为索引为零的账户是 `deployer`
So we'll say let i equals one is going to be less than let's say six. And we'll do i plus plus.
所以我们要写 `(let i = 1; i < 6; i++)`
And in here, we'll say const. And me contract Funmi connected contract equals await. And me dot connect two accounts, I,
在这里的内部，我们说 `const fundMeConnectedContract = await fundMe.connect(accounts[i])
so we need to call this connect function
我们需要调用这个 `connect` 函数
because right now if we scroll up back to the top,
因为现在，如果我们向上滚动到顶部
our Funmi contract is connected to our Deployer account.
我们的 `fundMe` 合约现在正与 `deployer` 账户连接
And anytime we call a transaction with Funmi,
因此无论何时只要我们使用 `fundMe` 调用交易
the deployer is the account that is calling that transaction,
交易的调用者就都是 `deployer`
we need to create new objects to connect to all of these different accounts.
我们需要创建新的对象来连接所有这些不同的账户
So we're gonna say fund me connected contract,
所以我们现在要使用 `fundMeConnectedContract`
which is now connected to one of these different accounts
它现在正连接在一个不同的账户上
dot fund. And this is where we'll do value, send value.
`.fund()`
Or excuse me, we'll do await.
抱歉，这里还有一个 `await`
Great. So this is going to be our our range section.
很好，这里就是我们的 "Arrange" 部分
And then same as we did above, we need to grab those starting balances.
接着就和上面一样，我们需要获取初始余额
So we can just copy that, those two lines and paste that down here.
我们可以直接复制这两行，并把它们粘贴到这里
Now we're going to move into act,
现在我们就要转到 "Act" 了
I'm going to call that withdrawal function again.
我们将再次调用 `withdraw` 函数
So let's say const, transaction action response equals await and MI dot withdraw.
`const transactionResponse = await fundMe.withdraw()`
And we're going to do the exact same thing as we did above,
接着我们就要做和上面完全相同的事了
getting the transaction receipt and the gas costs so we can get everything correct.
获取 `transactionReceipt` 以及 `gasCost` 以便我们可以确保一切正确
Once we've done the act, we move on into assert.
只要我们完成了 "Act" 就可以转到 "Assert" 上了
And we're going to do some very similar things to what we did above,
我们要做的事和上面很类似
like this, for example, this whole first part is going to be exactly the same.
比如说，第一部分是完全相同的
We also want to make sure the funders are reset properly.
但同时我们还希望 `funders` 可以正确重置
So we'll make sure that this funders array is reset properly.
所以我们要确保这个 `funders` 数组能正确重置
So to do that,
要做到这一点
we can actually just check to see that if looking at the zero with position throws an error
我们只需要检查一下位置零是否会报错就行了
so we can run a wait expect fund me dot get on me dot funder on me dot funders of zero.
所以我们可以运行 `await expect(fundMe.funders(0))`
This should revert
它应该会导致回滚
so we'll say await expect Funmi dot funders dot two dot b dot reverted
所以就是 `await expect(fundMe.funders(0)).to.be.reverted`
and then we want to loop through all these accounts
然后我们要遍历所有这些账户
and make sure that it makes sure or that in our mapping here, all their amounts are zero.
并要确保在我们的 `mapping` 中，它们的金额都是零
So we'll say, for I equals one is less than six, i plus plus,
所以就是 `for (i = 1; i< 6; i++)`
we'll say assert dot equal. Wait, fund me dot address to amount funded, of the accounts of I got address should be zero.
`assert.equal(await fundMe.addressToAmountFunded(accounts[i].address), 0)
So we're making sure that all of these mappings are correctly updated to zero.
我们正在确保所有这些 `mapping` 都能被正确更新为零
So let's go and test this.
让我们来测试一下
So we're withdrawing with multiple founders,
获取 "withdraw with multiple funders"
we're going to go back to our terminal,
回到我们的终端
we're going to hit up,
按一下上("↑")键
we're going to change this GREP or this one.
把 `grep` 改成这个
We'll see if this passes. And it does indeed,
看能不能通过测试，确实通过了！
so this means that our withdraw function works really well even when there's multiple funders
这就意味着我们的 `withdraw` 函数运行良好，即使是有多个资助者存在
and we can be happy and go to sleep knowing that.
这应该能让我们安心地睡个好觉了
Now the other thing we absolutely want 100% want to test
还有一个东西我们百分之一百要测试一下
is that our only owner modifier is working,
就是我们的 `onlyOwner` 修饰器是否有效
we want only the owner to be able to withdraw the funds from here.
我们希望只有拥有者才能从这里提取资金
So we'll create a new session,
所以我们来创建一个新的部分
we'll say it only allows the owner to withdraw only allows you to withdraw. This will be an async function.
`it("Only allows the owner to withdraw", async function() {})`
And in here, we'll say const. Accounts equals ethers dot get signers again.
这里我们再写一次 `const accounts = ethers.getSigners()`
And we'll say const attacker equals accounts of one.
然后是 `const attacker = accounts[1]`
So we'll say the first account will be some random attacker
我们假设第一个账户将成为一个随机的攻击者
will connect this attacker to a new contract,
我们要把这个 `attacker` 连接到一个新的合约上
we'll say const attacker connected contract equals await on DB dot Connect. Attacker dot address,
`const attackerConnectedContract = await fundMe.connect(attacker.address)`
excuse me a dot connect attacker.
抱歉，应该是 `.connect(attacker)`
Since we're not just connecting the address, we're connecting the account
因为我们不是连接到地址，而是连接到账户
which attacker is an account object.
`attacker` 是一个账户对象
And then we'll do a wait expect attacker connected contract dot withdraw dot two dot b dot reverted,
接着我们执行 `await expect(attackerConnectedContract.withdraw()).to.be.reverted`
they should not be able to withdraw.
它应该是不能提取的
So let's go ahead, we can even just copy this whole thing if we want
让我们继续，我们可以直接复制这一整句话，只要我们想的话
to hit up, we'll delete this section here.
按上("↑")键，删除这一部分
We'll paste that in.
粘贴进去
And boom. This means that when some other account tries to call withdraw, automatically gets reverted,
嘭，这意味着当某个其他账户尝试调用 `withdraw` 时，就会自动执行回滚
which is what we want.
这正是我们想要的
Now we can be more explicit to make sure that the correct error code is being thrown,
现在我们可以更加明确，要求抛出的是正确的错误代码
not just that it's reverted. Right,
而不仅仅只是执行了回滚，对吧
it can be very reverted because they sent ether did it they did something weird,
回滚可以是因为发送了以太币也可以是因为做了其它奇怪的事
we want to make sure it's reverted with our specific error code.
而我们想要确保的是它是因为某个特定的错误代码才回滚的
So right now we have this not owner error code.
现在我们有这么一个 `NotOwner` 错误代码
But it's actually a best practice
但实际上最好的做法应该是
to put the contract name to underscores and then your custom error.
把合约的名字和两个下划线放到你的自定义错误前
This makes it a lot easier in the future when you have a ton of different contracts,
这样做可以使未来处理大量不同合约时变得更加容易
and you're not sure where an error is coming from.
尤其是在你不确定错误来自于哪里的时候
So we're going to just update this really quickly to be fund me underscore underscore, not owner,
我们来快速更新一下这个 `FundMe__NotOwner()`
now we can do is now that we have this custom error,
现在我们有了这个自定义错误
we can say withdraw that to be reverted with,
就可以开始 `(withdraw()).to.be.revertedWith()
then we can add our custom error in here.
接着把我们的自定义错误添加进去
Now, if we rerun our test, with only allows the owner to withdraw,
现在，如果我们重新运行我们的测试，附带 "Only allows the owner to withdraw"
oops, we need to do a wait here. My mistake,
哎呀，这里需要有一个 `await`，我的错
wait a Thursday, get signers.
`await ethers.getSigners()`
And now let's try this again. And we are indeed passing Perfect.
我们来再试一次，确实通过了，完美！